http://www.dradept.com/privacy

x
Coronavirus Notice
We are continuing to work from home and manage our clients websites.
Please let us know if there is anything we can do during this transition phase back to working life.
We have created a Simple Cart System to allow our clients to sell quickly and simply online.  Find out more and get in touch if you would like to start trading online.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Website
Cookie Policy
We use Google Analytics
Opt-out
Disabling Cookies
Contact & Communication
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is for this website dradept.com and served by DRA and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners.  Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Website
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience.  This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
Cookie Policy
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website.  Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device.  This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer / device.
The cookies in use to deliver Google Analytics service are described in the table below.
We use Google Analytics
These cookies are used to store information, such as what time your current visit occurred, whether you have been to the site before, and what site referred you to the web page.
These cookies contain no personally identifiable information but they will use your computer's IP address to know from where in the world you are accessing the Internet.
Google stores the information collected by these cookies on servers in the United States.  Google may transfer this information to third-parties where required to do so by law, or where such third-parties process the information on Google's behalf.
Opt-out
In order to provide website visitors with more choice on how data is collected by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.  The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to stop data being sent to Google Analytics.  The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on does not affect usage of the website in any other way.  A link to further information on the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is provided below for your convenience.
tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=None
For more information on the usage of cookies by Google Analytics please see the Google website.  A link to the privacy advice for this product is provided below for your convenience.
www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html
Disabling Cookies
If you would like to restrict the use of cookies you can control this in your Internet browser.  Please check your browsers Preferences or Settings to enable/disable cookies.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk.  Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998.  Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted.  This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process.  Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to.  This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material.  Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
Email Newsletter
This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website.  Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion.  Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.
Subscriptions are taken in compliance with UK Spam Laws detailed in the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003.  All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.  No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website.  Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter program.  A small fee will be payable.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the business address at the bottom of this policy.
Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email.  Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation.  Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a comprehensive list].
This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.
In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe at any time through an automated system.  This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign.  If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to un-subscribe will by detailed instead.
You can unsubscribe at any time using the Mailing List page or if you prefer send an email to
from the email address you wish to be removed or Contact us.
External Links
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.  (External links are clickable text / banner / image links to other websites)
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts.  Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
Social Media Platforms
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.
Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details.  This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.
This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question.  Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
Shortened Links in Social Media
This website and its owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages.  By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy urls [web addresses] using third party apps such as bit.ly
Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened urls published on social media platforms by this website and its owners.  Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine urls are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.
Copyright Information
This site, its contents and the compilation (collection, arrangement, and assembly) is the property of DRA, and are protected by U.K.  and international copyright and trademark laws.  You agree not to alter the presentation, reproduce, retransmit, disseminate, sell, display, distribute, or exploit the information in any manner without the express written consent of DRA.
This information is for the personal use of our visitors only.  Commercial use or reprinting or transmitting this information whole or any part thereof, in any manner is prohibited without written permission from DRA.
DR Adept also respects the copyright and intellectual property rights of others.  We will remove any content from our site that infringes the copyright or other intellectual property rights of others.  If you believe that any material has been infringed on the DRA site, please Contact us.
Contacting DRA
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or Copyright Notice, the practices of our sites, or your dealings with this or other DRA Web sites please Contact us at DRA.
Ready to Transform Your
Website and Online Business
Get Started
Websites that Generate Leads and Increase Sales
from online stores, booking systems, and calendars, to generating revenue, nurturing a community of fans, and promoting your brand.  A website is the centre of any business that wants to survive in the online world.  You can't afford not to have one.
Contact us Now for a FREE Quote
Our Privacy Policy
×
Coronavirus Notice
We are continuing to work from home and manage our clients websites.
Please let us know if there is anything we can do during this transition phase back to working life.
We have created a Simple Cart System to allow our clients to sell quickly and simply online.  Find out more and get in touch if you would like to start trading online.
×
